nhm.gov.in 2019-07-14

# Privacy Policy :: National Health Mission

Though all efforts have been made to ensure the accuracy of the content on this website, the same should not be construed as a statement of law or used for any legal purposes. Ministry of Health  & Family Welfare accepts no responsibility in relation to the accuracy, completeness, usefulness or otherwise, of the contents. Users are advised to verify/check any information, and to obtain any appropriate professional advice before acting on the information provided on this website.

Ministry of Health & Family Welfare website does not automatically capture any specific personal information from any user (like name, phone no. or e-mail address) that allows this Ministry to identify any user individually when users visit the site. Users can generally visit the site without revealing Personal Information, unless users choose to provide such information.

**Site Visit data**

This website records user’s visit and logs the following information for statistical purposes -users server’s address; the name of the top-level domain from which users access the Internet (for example, .gov, .com, .in, etc.); the type of browser users use; the date and time users access the site; the pages users have accessed and the documents downloaded and the previous Internet address from which users linked directly to the site.

We will not identify users or their browsing activities, except when a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect the service provider’s logs.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of software code that an internet web site sends to user’s browser when users access information at that site. This website does not use cookies.

**Email Management**

User’s email address will only be recorded if users choose to send a message. It will only be used for the purpose for which users have provided it and will not be added to a mailing list. Website user’s email address will not be used for any other purpose, and will not be disclosed, without user’s consent.

**Collection of Personal Information**

If users are asked for any other Personal Information users will be informed how it will be used if users choose to give it. If at any time users believe the principles referred to in this privacy statement have not been followed, or have any other comments on these principles, please notify the webmaster through the contact us page.

**Note** :The use of the term "Personal Information" in this privacy statement refers to any information from which user’s identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained.
